ILGWU 4x5 Negatives of Photographs 5780 P N45
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series Dubinsky
  - DAVID DUBINSKY with Netherlands visitors Health Center and Luncheon WM Dress Premier, B.T. DeJong Secretary and Jan H. Van Royen Ambassador, 1/15/52 (item: DD104), 1952 (Box 19, Folder 104)
  - Pictures of DAVID DUBINSKY at Pictorial Biography, 1952 (item: DD105) (Box 19, Folder 105)
  - Local 32 1st Retirement Luncheon, 1952 (item: DD106) (Box 19, Folder 106)
  - DAVID DUBINSKY gets scroll from Silvio Ascari the Secretary General of Italian Clothing Workers Free Union and Fabio Tonolli the Secretary Organizer. (item: DD107), 1952 (Box 19, Folder 107)
    Scroll made by one of their memebers, June 3, 1952
  - DAVID DUBINSKYs 60th Birthday Waldorf Astoria GEB and Managers, 2/21/52 (item: DD108), 1952 (Box 19, Folder 108)
  - David Dubinsky 60th Birthday Press Conference, 2/21/52 (item: DD109), 1952 (Box 19, Folder 109)
  - Workman circle old age home dedication. President of W.C. Home, Jacob Roberts and DAVID DUBINSKY at Erlich and Alter Bronze, 3/2/52 (item: DD110), 1952 (Box 19, Folder 110)
  - Dubinsky with gavel at meeting, 3/19/52 (item: DD111) (Box 19, Folder 111)
  - Unknown (item: DD112) (Box 19, Folder 112)
  - Workman circle lunch at the Astor Hotel Adolph Scherf Vice Chancellor of Austria, Jules March French delegate to the United Nations, 3/19/52 (item: DD113) (Box 19, Folder 113)
  - Augustus Cool the president of Confederation of Christian Trade Union of Belgium 4/4/1952 (item: DD114) (Box 19, Folder 114)
    Also, Isidore Nagler becomes Manager of Cloak Eexecutive Joint Board DAVID DUBINSKY congratulates him, 4/30/52
  - JLC Headquarters opening, 5/9/52 (item: DD115), 1952 (Box 19, Folder 115)
  - Joint Executive Board of Cloak, 8/19/52 (item: DD116) (Box 19, Folder 116)
  - New York State Committee Liberal Party Statler Hotel Stevenson Accepts Nomination, 8/28/52 (item: DD117), 1952 (Box 19, Folder 117)
  - AFL Convention President Eisenhower, 9/15/52 (item: DD118), 1952 (Box 19, Folder 118)
  - AFL in New York, 9/15/52 (item: DD119), 1952 (Box 19, Folder 119)
  - 50th Anniversary of Local 10 Carnegie Hall, 10/5/52 (item: DD120), 1952 (Box 19, Folder 120)
  - Stevenson Rally in Garment Center 36th and 7th, 10/28/52 (item: DD121), 1952 (Box 19, Folder 121)
  - Stevenson, Bankhead, 10/28/52 (item: DD122), 1952 (Box 19, Folder 122)
  - Political Tallulah Bankhead, Addi Stevenson on ABC Elysee Studio, 202 West 58th Street, 10/28/52 (item: DD123), 1952 (Box 19, Folder 123)
  - Local 22 Political Rally, 10/29/52 (item: DD124), 1952 (Box 19, Folder 124)
  - ICFTU Michael Rass, Director of International Affairs CIO George Meany the President of AFL and DAVID DUBINSKY, 12/1/52 (item: DD125), 1952 (Box 19, Folder 125)
  - Eastern Regional Retirement Fund Conference, 12/5/52 (item: DD126), 1952 (Box 19, Folder 126)
  - Local 91 Retirees, 1/7/53 (item: DD127), 1953 (Box 19, Folder 127)
  - Local 62 Retirees, 1/12/53 (item: DD128), 1953 (Box 19, Folder 128)
  - Local 22 Installation Dave Schulkin, 3/4/53 (item: DD129), 1953 (Box 19, Folder 129)
  - Local 117 Installation, 3/11/53 (item: DD130), 1953 (Box 19, Folder 130)
  - Local 35 Installation, 3/17/53 (item: DD131), 1953 (Box 19, Folder 131)
  - Local 10 Installation, 3/23/53 (item: DD132), 1953 (Box 19, Folder 132)
  - Cloak Joint Board Installation DAVID DUBINSKY Isidore Nagler as General Manage,r 3/25/53 (item: DD133), 1953 (Box 19, Folder 133)
  - Local 59 Installation 3/28/53 (item: DD134), 1953 (Box 19, Folder 134)
  - Dress Joint Board Installation DAVID DUBINSKY installs Hochman and Minkoff at Hotel Astor, 4/8/53 (item: DD135), 1953 (Box 19, Folder 135)
  - Eastern Out of Town Installation, 4/10/53 (item: DD136), 1953 (Box 19, Folder 136)
  - DAVID DUBINSKY visited by Montreal, Canada employees with Bernard Shove, 4/15/53 (item: DD137), 1953 (Box 19, Folder 137)
  - Local 132 Official opening of new headquarters 7-9- West 18th Street DAVID DUBINSKY and Martin Feldman, 4/15/53 (item: DD138), 1953 (Box 19, Folder 138)
  - 60th Birthday gift from Histradrut A. Kahn and I. Hamlin, 5/8/53 (item: DD139), 1953 (Box 19, Folder 139)
  - Testimonial to Durkin and Meany, 4/25/53 (item: DD140), 1953 (Box 19, Folder 140)
  - Liberal Party Annual Dinner Hotel Co in the General ballroom with Adolph Berle, Senator Morris Halley, DAVID DUBINSKY, Hogerty, Dorothy Schiff and L. Stulberg, 6/17/53 (item: DD141), 1953 (Box 19, Folder 141)
  - DAVID DUBINSKY speaking at Antonini 70th birthday celebration, 9/12/53 (item: DD142), 1953 (Box 19, Folder 142)
  - DAVID DUBINSKY meeting with Halley and New York officers at 1710 studio A, 10/16/53 (item: DD143), 1953 (Box 19, Folder 143)
  - Local 32 signs contract for 35 hours a week with no reduction in pay, meaning about 6% increase in pay. (item: DD144), 1953 (Box 19, Folder 144)
    Seated Exec director of Association Jed Silbert, President of Association Max Ladenheimer, DAVID DUBINSKY Manager of Local 32 Abraham Snyder, Manager of Local 10 Mae Ralikman; Standing: Attorney of Association Mel Kleeblat and the Attorney for the union E
  - Italian Garment workers with DAVID DUBINSKY F.O.A., 11/8/53 (item: DD145), 1953 (Box 19, Folder 145)
  - DAVID DUBINSKY speaking at mike, hand up North East Annual party, 12/12/53 (item: DD146), 1953 (Box 19, Folder 146)
  - North East Annual party Baltimore, 12/12/53 (item: DD147), 1953 (Box 19, Folder 147)
  - Local 91 40th Anniversary, 12/12/53 (item: DD148), 1953 (Box 19, Folder 148)
  - Baltimore Delegation Negotiation Committee in DAVID DUBINSKYs office, 12/14/53 (item: DD149), 1953 (Box 19, Folder 149)
  - DAVID DUBINSKY and Training Institute, 2/23/52 (item: DD150), 1952 (Box 19, Folder 150)
  - Local 9 Retires 180 member, 3/11/54 (item: DD151), 1954 (Box 19, Folder 151)
  - Local 99 Installation, 3/15/54 (item: DD152), 1954 (Box 19, Folder 152)
  - Worlds Fair Tickets, Umhey (item: DD153) (Box 19, Folder 153)
  - Jewish Labor Committee luncheon Professor Dr. Carla Schmidt, Fritz Erler, Guenther Klein, 4/8/54 (item: DD154), 1954 (Box 19, Folder 154)
  - L.I.D Award to Meany and Morse, 4/10/54 (item: DD155), 1954 (Box 19, Folder 155)
  - Nathan Margolies 60th birthday party given by Dress Joint Board, 4/9/54 (item: DD156), 1954 (Box 19, Folder 156)
  - Liberal Party Annual Dinner Stulberg, Counts, Rose and Franklin D. Roosevelt Jr, DAVID DUBINSKY and Guild members, 5/26/54 (item: DD157), 1954 (Box 19, Folder 157)
  - DAVID DUBINSKY speaking at training institute exercises, 6/54 (item: DD158), 1954 (Box 19, Folder 158)
  - DAVID DUBINSKY gets Page One Award Rosenstock, Murphy and Potoker, 6/9/54 (item: DD159), 1954 (Box 19, Folder 159)
  - National Urban League and AFL meeting in DAVID DUBINSKYs office, National Urban League 1133 Broadway Room 826 A. Thomas, 6/24/54 (item: DD160), 1954 (Box 19, Folder 160)
  - S. Farber 70th Birthday Park Sheraton, 8/5/54 (item: DD161), 1954 (Box 19, Folder 161)
  - Political Rally 38th to 7th Avenue Harriman, Franklin D. Roosevelt Jr. and M. Truman, 10/5/54 (item: DD161b), 1954 (Box 19, Folder 161b)
  - Cloak Contract Renewal in DAVID DUBINSKYs office American Coat and Suit management association 450 7th Avenue William Shanies, 10/6/54 (item: DD162), 1954 (Box 19, Folder 162)
  - Mobile Health Center, 12/13/54 (item: DD163), 1954 (Box 19, Folder 163)
  - Health mobile 10/12/54 to 10/13/54 (item: DD164), 1954 (Box 19, Folder 164)
  - Liberal Party Rally Stevenson, Harriman and Franklin D. Roosevelt Jr. Manhattan Center, 10/29/54 (item: DD165), 1954 (Box 19, Folder 165)
  - Italian Labor Committee Birthday Party for M. Woll 75, 1/8/55 (item: DD166), 1955 (Box 19, Folder 166)
  - Minimum Wage Washington Delegate and AFL Unity Committee, 3/55 (item: DD167), 1955 (Box 19, Folder 167)
  - Minimum Wage Washington (item: DD168) (Box 19, Folder 168)
  - ICF to Convention, 3/55 (item: DD169), 1955 (Box 19, Folder 169)
  - David Dubinsky, Meany and their wives in Europe at IFTCU May 1955 (item: DD170) (Box 19, Folder 170)
  - ILG Housing Controllers Office signing, 5/6/55 (item: DD171), 1955 (Box 19, Folder 171)
  - Unity House Theater Opening, 6/1/56 (item: DD172), 1956 (Box 19, Folder 172)
  - David Dubinsky returns from Israel ICFTU Vienna Congress DD and Potofsky, 6/27/55 (item: DD173), 1955 (Box 19, Folder 173)
  - Reports on ICFTU meeting and Israel visit, 6/29/55 (item: DD174), 1955 (Box 19, Folder 174)
  - David Dubinsky speaking on minimum wage Puerto Rico meeting (item: DD175) (Box 19, Folder 175)
  - Jewish Labor Committee lunch in honor of Guy Mollet Secretary General French Socialist Party. (item: DD176), 195 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    Julius Moch, Chief U.N. Delegate on disarmament, DAVID DUBINKY, Adolph Hald hat chair, JLC and Guy Mollet, September 5, 1955
  - JLC luncheon Guy Mollet (item: DD177) (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Memorial Hospital Donation Laurence S. Rockefeller $5,000 cancer fund, 9/25/56 (item: DD178), 1956 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - ILG Financial Press Conference Chase Manhattan Bank $20,000,000 invested in Home Mortgages, 9/26/56 (item: DD179), 1956 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - ILG gives 1 million dollars for hospital, $50,000 for sports arena and $50,000 for school, 12/20/55 (item: DD180), 1955 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - AFL- CIO Convention, 12/55 (item: DD181), 1955 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - AFL CIO Convention, 12/55 (item: DD182), 1955 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - AFL CIO Industrial Bulletin Cocktail Party for Harriman, 12/55 (item: DD183), 1955 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - AFL CIO Council meeting in Miami Florida Justice Issue, 3/1/56 (item: DD184), 1956 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Submarine, 3/1/56 (item: DD185), 1956 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Students of Columbia School of Journalism visit DAVID DUBINKY, 3/5/56 (item: DD186), 1956 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Local 10 Installation by DAVID DUBINKY Manhattan Center, 3/12/56 (item: DD187), 1956 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Local 9 Installation Harry Risler and Louis Hyman by DAVID DUBINKY, 3/13/56 (item: DD188), 1956 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Local 22 Installation by DAVID DUBINKY, Aba Eban Israel ambassador to U.S. Chief delegate to the United Nations from Israel, 3/14/56 (item: DD189), 1956 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Local 66 Installation, 4/9/56 (item: DD190), 1956 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - EDT Installation, 4/14/56 (item: DD191), 1956 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Local 62 Stulberg dinner 5/22/56 (item: DD192), 1956 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Contract Renewal in DAVID DUBINKYs office, 6/28/56 (item: DD193), 1956 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - ILG Gift of $250,000 to Dr. Biegen, National Secretary of the National Committee for Labor Israel for Histradrut Hospital, 6/29/56 (item: DD194), 1956 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Liberal Party Convention Manhattan Center, 9/11/56 (item: DD195), 1956 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - ILG Luncheon honoring Lehmans retirement from Senate and donation of $80,000 for Liberal Party candidates TV and radio expenses, 9/21/56 (item: DD196), 1956 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Liberal Party Womens Division for Stevenson, 10/24/56 (item: DD197), 1956 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - DAVID DUBINKY and G. Meany South American Tour, 11/8/56 (item: DD198), 1956 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Stevenson Rally Manhattan Center rained out 34th to 40th, 10/31/56 (item: DD199), 1956 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - AFL CIO Community Service Award to Lehman, 12/11/56 (item: DD200), 1956 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - City of Hope Dinner for, 12/13/56 (item: DD201), 1956 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - DAVID DUBINKYs Birthday party 65th by NY Board GEB Waldorf Astoria luncheon (item: DD202) (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - DAVID DUBINKYs 65th Birthday Lillian Russell, 2/21/57 (item: DD203), 1957 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Histradrut honors George Meany (item: DD204), 1957 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    Accepts Histradrut Humanitarian Award from Dr. Beig United Nations Secretary National Committee for Labor Israel. Joseph Schlassberg, Meany and DAVID DUBINKY, March 1957
  - Speaking to the Staff Ethical Practices, 4/57 (item: DD205), 1957 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - DDs House, Hampton Bays, 9/28/57 (item: DD206), 1957 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Local 105 Aid Europes Children with clothing, 1950 (item: DD207) (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Dubinsky and Eddie Cantor 1950 Convention (item: DD208) (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Dubinsky gives $25,000 to memorial hospital Mrs. Edward C. Delafield, chairman Dental Clinic, 6/25/50 (item: DD209), 1950 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Liberal Party Rally Manhattan Center Lynch and Pecora, 10/5/50 (item: DD210), 1950 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Dubinsky clone in Convention Hotel Atlantic City June 1950 (item: DD211) (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - 1950 Convention Rubins import of kids Local 129, Long Island (item: DD212) (Box 20, Folder 37)
- Series Eastern out of town
  - Women holding Port Chester Guide Newspaper displaying headline We Want Decent standards Demand Ladies Garment Strikers (item: EO1) (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Sadie Reich Head (item: EO2) (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Strike Committee of Oster and Seigel Jersey City, 9/23/50 (item: EO3), 1950 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Exquisite Brassiere negotiating Committee, 12/13/50 (item: EO4), 1950 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Pleasant Coat and Suit Company Clifton, New Jersey workers visit ILG Headquarters, 12/11/49 (item: EO5), 1949 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Casting Harry Rubenstein ILGWU Wander Plaque 1710 Broadway (item: EO6) (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Contract Signing by I. Horowitz Watertown underwear Committee look on with State Manager Samuel Janis, 1/13/54 (item: EO7), 1954 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Portrait (item: EO8) (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Israel Horowitz appointed manager at Eastern out of town department, 10/51 (item: EO9), 1951 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Meeting (item: EO10) (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Staff (item: EO11) (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Wander and family Birthday party (item: EO12) (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Hochman Report on new agreement demands, 10/50 (item: EO13), 1950 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Wander and company (item: EO14) (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Dancing (item: EO15) (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - Staff at pool (item: EO16) (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - Female choir (item: EO17) (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - Wander presenting gifts (item: EO18) (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - Contract signing (item: EO19) (Box 20, Folder 56)
  - Womens meeting/class (item: EO20) (Box 20, Folder 57)
  - Male portrait at office (item: EO21) (Box 20, Folder 58)
  - Contract signing Dubinsky (item: EO22) (Box 20, Folder 59)
  - Seated group photo shoot (item: EO23) (Box 20, Folder 60)
  - Small group talking (item: EO24) (Box 20, Folder 61)
  - Wander and others (item: EO25) (Box 20, Folder 62)
  - Contract signing Dubinsky (item: EO26) (Box 20, Folder 63)
  - EASTERN OUT OF TOWN. Long Island (item: EO27) (Box 20, Folder 64)
  - Large group portrait Dubinsky seated center (item: EO28) (Box 20, Folder 65)
  - Group being addressed (item: EO29) (Box 20, Folder 66)
  - Contract signing New Jersey State Educational Conference (item: EO30) (Box 20, Folder 67)
  - Group photo Wrangler (item: EO31) (Box 20, Folder 68)
  - Misc. Wrangler award, presentation and meeting in office (item: EO32) (Box 20, Folder 69)
  - EASTERN OUT OF TOWN. at Unity, 6/23 to 25/50 (item: EO33), 1950 (Box 20, Folder 70)
  - EASTERN OUT OF TOWN. New York Staff Convention Report 1956, March (item: EO34) (Box 20, Folder 71)
  - EASTERN OUT OF TOWN. Groups (item: EO35) (Box 20, Folder 72)
  - EASTERN OUT OF TOWN Weekend at Unity House Wander (item: EO36) (Box 20, Folder 73)
  - EASTERN OUT OF TOWN. maid uniform Brassiere negotiating, 12/14/50 (item: EO37), 1950 (Box 20, Folder 74)
  - Women seated indoors (item: EO38) (Box 20, Folder 75)
  - Maid uniform negotiations (item: EO39) (Box 20, Folder 76)
  - Womens pageant (item: EO40) (Box 20, Folder 77)
  - Meeting (item: EO41) (Box 20, Folder 78)
  - Wander and others at a dinner table portrait (item: EO42) (Box 20, Folder 79)
  - EASTERN OUT OF TOWN staff (item: EO43) (Box 20, Folder 80)
- Series Education
  - Man and woman presenting to the class (item: EA1) (Box 20, Folder 81)
  - Dead End kids list making 1. Bad housing, 2. Crime, 3 to 5. Blank (item: EA2) (Box 20, Folder 82)
  - Hudson shore meeting (item: EA3) (Box 20, Folder 83)
  - Mark Starr lectures 30 superintendents from 13 states attending a in-service course at Tea Collidge, 7/18/50 (item: EA4), 1950 (Box 20, Folder 84)
  - Jewish Seminary students with Mark Starr, 1951 (item: EA5) (Box 20, Folder 85)
  - Local 60 Education ICFTU around the world with labor, 12/13/50 (item: EA6), 1950 (Box 20, Folder 86)
  - Stockridge Private school of Interlaken, MA. Student visit ILG, sees movie and asks questions, 11/22/50 (item: EA7), 1950 (Box 20, Folder 87)
  - Educational Department ILG movie With these hands, 12/12/50 (item: EA8), 1950 (Box 20, Folder 88)
  - In-service Training Institute Radio and mimeograph work shop Beatrice Paipert Robert Thege, Vincent Vicari and Rose Terry, 7/19/51 (item: EA9) (Box 20, Folder 89)
  - Education Department Randolph Goodman Columbia, 11/28/51 (item: EA10), 1951 (Box 20, Folder 90)
  - Local 38 Roger Baldwin on Civil Liberties in a Mobilization Economy, 1/16/52 (item: EA11), 1952 (Box 20, Folder 91)
  - Two women reading a poster for the Volunteer (item: EA12) (Box 20, Folder 92)
  - Outdoor Lecture (item: EA13) (Box 20, Folder 93)
  - Activity Outdoors (item: EA14) (Box 20, Folder 94)
  - Learn to vote table (item: EA15) (Box 20, Folder 95)
  - Men and women receiving books (item: EA16) (Box 20, Folder 96)
  - Books and reports (item: EA17) (Box 20, Folder 97)
  - Small class Union Health center pamphlets (item: EA18) (Box 20, Folder 98)
  - Women in a reading room (item: EA19) (Box 20, Folder 99)
  - Musicians practicing and smoking (item: EA20) (Box 20, Folder 100)
  - Man lecturing female class (item: EA21) (Box 20, Folder 101)
  - An American Looks at England (item: EA22), 1949 (Box 20, Folder 102)
    ILG teacher Julius Manson, who just returned from four months in Europe, gave members a bird's eye view of what the British government is doing in the way of health insurance, nationalization of industry, etc., at ILGWU headquarters last month. Fannia Coh
  - Mark Starr (item: EA23) (Box 20, Folder 103)
  - Immigrant course (item: EA24) (Box 20, Folder 104)
  - Meeting (item: EA25) (Box 20, Folder 105)
  - Small class (item: EA26) (Box 20, Folder 106)
  - Two girls filling out cards in Studio A, Mark Starr looks on (item: EA27) (Box 20, Folder 107)
  - Unites Nations Report: The problem of Greece (item: EA28) (Box 20, Folder 108)
  - Woman playing Labor game (item: EA29) (Box 20, Folder 109)
  - Small lecture (item: EA30) (Box 20, Folder 110)
  - Women working in office (item: EA31) (Box 20, Folder 111)
  - Local 62 history (item: EA32) (Box 20, Folder 112)
  - Women in reading room (item: EA33) (Box 20, Folder 113)
  - Lecture (item: EA34) (Box 20, Folder 114)
  - Educational Library, 11/54 (item: EA35) (Box 20, Folder 115)
  - Local 155 Church and Company Lunch hour Education on retirement Max Stamler from Social Security Building briefs workers on their due benefits under the law, 11/21/50 (item: EA36), 1950 (Box 20, Folder 116)
  - Photo mosaic (item: EA37) (Box 20, Folder 117)
  - Mark Starr lecturing (item: EA38) (Box 20, Folder 118)
  - Members on a boat (item: EA39) (Box 20, Folder 119)
  - Recreational Wilkes Barre Buttons and bows Chorus and swimsuit models (item: EA40) (Box 20, Folder 120)
  - Health Lecture (item: EA41) (Box 20, Folder 121)
  - ILGWU Junior League Lick Em All (item: EA42), 1945 (Box 20, Folder 122)
    Sucking away at lollipops a group of children of ILGWU members assembled at the union's get a front seat view of Macy's annual parade through the city's main street, December 1, 45
  - Women in library (item: EA43) (Box 20, Folder 123)
  - Halloween High-Jinx at Local 38 Canteen (item: EA44), 1945 (Box 20, Folder 124)
    Profiting by experience in sinking the Jap fleet, this Navy guest comes up triumphantly with the traditional apple at a party given to servicemen by the Ladies' Tailors. At right, Selma Sachs, at the union staff, applauds the sailor's apple appetite, Nove
  - Library (item: EA45), 1951 (Box 20, Folder 125)
  - Pique Ohio ILGers visit ILG, 2/16/51 (item: EA46), 1951 (Box 20, Folder 126)
  - Lecturer Inter-Christian Collegiate Council and Theological Seminary Students at Studio A, 7/36/51 (item: EA47), 1951 (Box 20, Folder 127)
  - FM Cohn Hunter College and Harry Rubenstein, 2/7/59 (item: EA48), 1959 (Box 20, Folder 128)
  - 21st Birthday celebration The Future of the world lies in the hands of intelligent and well informed workers (item: EA49) (Box 20, Folder 129)
  - Fall English Lesson (item: EA50) (Box 20, Folder 130)
  - Ruth Warren Education Director, Kentucky and Starr Negro History week, 2/16/51 (item: EA51), 1951 (Box 20, Folder 131)
  - ILG member lend support to Rural schools Inc. Ex. Secretary Rae Brandstein in Center, 10/23/51 (item: EA52), 1951 (Box 20, Folder 132)
  - Teacher Rhoda Sakin daughter Local 38 PS 177 With the hands, 5/9/51 (item: EA53), 1951 (Box 20, Folder 133)
  - Women in library (item: EA54) (Box 20, Folder 134)
  - Lecture on How social security works (item: EA55) (Box 20, Folder 135)
  - Visitors Nancy Adams British Trade Union Congress officer Lecturer on Women in TV, 4/22/52 (item: EA56), 1952 (Box 20, Folder 136)
  - Stern speaking to French trade union (item: EA57) (Box 20, Folder 137)
  - Stan Levy and Columbia School of Journalism students Adolph Held and David Dubinsky, 3/5/56 (item: EA58), 1956 (Box 20, Folder 138)
  - OQ class, 12/58 (item: EA59), 1958 (Box 20, Folder 139)
  - International Women Exposition of Hand Art, 71st Armory, 34th and Park Avenue, 11/4/54 (item: EA60), 1954 (Box 20, Folder 140)
  - Cohn 50th Anniversary of Waist Makers Suppressing meet at Cooper Union, 11/14/59 (item: EA61), 1959 (Box 20, Folder 141)
  - Fire wardens meeting Lieutenant Klein, 9/24/59 (item: EA62), 1959 (Box 20, Folder 142)
  - Cohn Lecture, 8/18/59 (item: EA63) (Box 20, Folder 143)
  - How to be even better looking than usual thats the aim of Club 22s course in Grooming for Modern Woman (item: EA64) (Box 20, Folder 144)
    Given by Mrs. Beulah Niebukr, beauty authority for Dermetics Inc., as she demonstrates on Elsie Leitner of Local 22 Dress makers"
  - Learn to vote table FDR Roosevelt Campaign (item: EA65) (Box 20, Folder 145)
  - Local 22 Education night meeting Center Hotel, 10/38 (item: EA66), 1938 (Box 20, Folder 146)
  - Apples on a string (item: EA67) (Box 20, Folder 147)
  - Labor Library (item: EA68) (Box 20, Folder 148)
  - Local 22 Spanish Lecture (item: EA69) (Box 20, Folder 149)
  - F.M. Cohn New York University Dr. Monroe Berger Why do people join mass movements, 12/8/51 (item: EA70), 1951 (Box 20, Folder 150)
  - Eleanor Roosevelt and Fannia M. Cohen at UN lecture January 22, 1955 (item: EA71) (Box 20, Folder 151)
- Series Educational Meetings
  - Lunch hour lecture in shop (item: EM1) (Box 20, Folder 152)
  - South Jersey Joint Board at United Nations Tour, 4/19/58 (item: EM2) (Box 20, Folder 153)
  - Local 25 UN Tour February 16, 1957 Dr. Frank P. Graham and Chaskrender, FM Cohen and Louis Quintilimo economic and social council (item: EM3) (Box 20, Folder 154)
  - Educational meeting at UN speaker Herrick Information office, 9/22/51 (item: EM4), 1951 (Box 20, Folder 155)
  - Local 117 at United Nations (item: EM5) (Box 20, Folder 156)
  - Norman Solol Director of United Nations, America for Service for the UN Tony Sander ICFTU, Representative Mark Starr delegate to United Nations, 11/55 (item: EM6), 1955 (Box 20, Folder 157)
  - Department of Public Info at United Nations, 1952 (item: EM7) (Box 20, Folder 158)
  - U.N.O. (item: EM8) (Box 20, Folder 159)
  - UNITED NATIONS Visits Miss Cohn, 1955 (item: EM9) (Box 20, Folder 160)
  - New York University Visitors, 1951 (item: EM10) (Box 20, Folder 161)
  - Cohn Cooper Union February 24, 1951 (item: EM11) (Box 20, Folder 162)